Guide to the Turkish Photography Collection 1910-1990 AD.MC.007
AbuDhabi
- Three females of varying ages standing in front of a field of corn. 13.8 x 9.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 1)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Women
- A young male in a suit, leaning on a tree with water in the background. 14.0 x 9.1 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 1)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Men; Photographic Prints; Suits; Trees; Turkey
- A young female in a dress holding onto a tree under a wooden deck. 13.5 x 8.6 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 1)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Individual Portraits; Nature; Photographic Prints; Trees; Turkey
- A young male wearing a suit and cloack with knotted buttons. Foto Lale, Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey. 13.4 x 8.6 cm, Undated; Studio Foto Lale, Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey (Box 6, Folder 1)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Istanbul, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Uniforms
- A family group standing in front of some bushes on pavement. 13.8 x 9.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 1)
  Family Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Streets; Turkey
- A young female in a dark outfit, holding a book in front of some trees. 13.8 x 8.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 1)
  Books; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Women
- A young baby in a light outfit making a funny face. 13.7 x 8.7 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 1)
- A young child in a plaid shirt, holding a small briefcase. 13.9 x 9.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 1)
  Boys; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Turkey
- An older male embracing a young female in a black dress in front of a mural of deers. 13.9 x 9.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 2)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Men; Photographic Prints; Turkey
- A young female sitting on a wall in Kulturpark, Izmir, Turkey. 13.8 x 9.1 cm, Undated; Studio Kulturpark, Izmir, Turkey (Box 6, Folder 2)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Izmir, Turkey; Parks; Photographic Prints; Statues; Women
- Three young females in the same dress in front of a building. 14.0 x 9.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 2)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Uniforms; Women
- A family group of three, with a young girl holding a cat. 13.2 x 8.5 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 2)
  Cats; Family Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Nature; Photographic Prints; Turkey
- A group of men in winter coats, walking in the snow, holding something wrapped in a white sheet. 14.0 x 9.2 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 2)
  Coats; Gatherings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Snow; Turkey
- An older lady with a blonde wig standing in a parking lot. Turkish writing on the back. Cinarcik, Yalova, Turkey. 13.8 x 9.0 cm, 19 May 1977; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 2)
  Cars; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Streets; Women; Yalova, Turkey
- A standing older male embracing two younger males in striped sweaters. Turkish writing on the back. 13.5 x 8.6 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 2)
  Boys; Family Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkey; Turkish Writing
- A family group of four. Older female and younger female in patterned dresses. Turkish writing on the back. 13.6 x 8.7 cm, 10 April 1959; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 2)
  Children; Family Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkey; Turkish Writing
- An older woman in a floral patterned dress holding a baby on her shoulder, standing in front of a car. Turkish writing. 13.7 x 8.7 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 2)
  Cars; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Turkish Writing; Women
- An older female in a black dress with an ornate broach at the breast. Turkish writing on the back. 14.0 x 8.8 cm, 15 May 1940; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Three females in long coats standing in front of a circular flower arrangement. Foto Lüks, Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey. 13.5 x 8.5 cm, Undated; Studio Foto Luks, Turkey (Box 6, Folder 3)
  Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey; Coats; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Women
- A family group of five posing in front of a large tree, two young males are wearing military uniforms. Ottoman writing on the back. 13.8 x 9.0 cm, 1920; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 3)
  Children; Family; Gelatin Silver Prints; Military; Nature; Ottoman Writing; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Uniforms
- An older couple, female in a black satin dress is seated while male is standing and embracing her. Turkish writing on reverse. Studio Hamza Rustem, Izmir, Turkey. 13.5 x 8.5 cm, 1953; Studio Nuri Hamza Rustem Fotografhanesi, Izmir, Turkey (Box 6, Folder 3)
  Couple; Gelatin Silver Prints; Izmir, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkish Writing
- A female in a white dress with matching gloves and male in a white tails jacket. Turkish writing on the back. 13.9 x 9.0 cm, 22 August 1970; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 3)
  Couple; Gelatin Silver Prints; Gloves; Party; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Turkish Writing
- A young girl in a long white dress with short puffy sleeves and a large bow in her hair. Foto Teknik Galip Anilmis, Istanbul, Turkey. 13.5 x 8.3 cm, Undated; Studio Foto Teknik, Turkey (Box 6, Folder 3)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Individual Portraits; Istanbul, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
- A young female in a dark coat holding up a young baby on a cover table. Turkish writing on the reverse. 13.3 x 8.3 cm, 9 January 1946; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 3)
- A young male in a short winter coat standing on the sidewalk pointing a gun at the camera. Turkish writing on the back. 14.1 x 9.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 3)
  Boys; Gelatin Silver Prints; Guns; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Streets; Turkey; Turkish Writing
- An older couple dancing. Foto Venüs, Eskisehir, Turkey. Turkish writing on reverse. Circumcision party. 13.7 x 8.5 cm, 13 September 1957; Studio Venus, Turkey (Box 6, Folder 3)
  Couple; Dancing; Eskisehir, Turkey; Gelatin Silver Prints; Party; Photographic Prints
- A bride and groom standing behind an older steated couple. Foto Emel, Besiktas, Istanbul, Turkey. 13.9 x 9.0 cm, Undated; Studio Foto Emel, Istanbul, Turkey (Box 6, Folder 3)
  Bebek, Istanbul, Turkey; Couple; Family; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Wedding Portraits
- A little girl in a flannel dress standing on a table with wood paneling in the background. Ottoman writing. 14.0 x 8.9 cm, 17 March 1929; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 4)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Individual Portraits; Ottoman Writing; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
- A bride with a floor length veil standing in front of a large flower arrangement and patterned wallpaper. Turkish writing. Hilton, Istanbul, Turkey. 13.9 x 9.0 cm, 26 June 1955; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 4)
  Brides; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Turkish Writing; Wedding Portraits
- A couple, female is seated on a carpet covered stool. Foto Rekor, Beyoglu, Turkey. Ottoman writing. 13.7 x 8.6 cm, 25 August 1933; Studio Foto Rekor, Turkey (Box 6, Folder 4)
  Couple; Gelatin Silver Prints; Istanbul, Turkey; Ottoman Writing; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
- A female walking down a flight of stairs in a dress. Foto Rekor, Adapazari, Turkey. 13.7 x 8.7 cm, Undated; Studio Foto Rekor, Adapazari, Turkey (Box 6, Folder 4)
  Adapazari, Turkey; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
- A young female in a sweater with a necklace hidden under her sweater and short dark hair. Turkish writing on the back. Suadiye, Istanbul, Turkey. 13.5 x 8.5 cm, 12 February 1937; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 4)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Istanbul, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkish Writing; Women
- A group of five posing under a tree against a large wooden building. 13.9 x 8.9 cm, 3 May 1942; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 4)
  Family; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Nature; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Turkish Writing
- Two females wearing the same sleeveless dress, with an older male pinning sashes on the dress. Marine Club, Graduation Ceremony. Turkish writing on the back. 13.6 x 8.6 cm, 2 October 1966; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 4)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Turkish Writing; Women
- Two older couples standing in front of a stairway with two men climbing the stairs. Foto Lüks. 13.5 x 8.3 cm, Undated; Studio Foto Luks, Turkey (Box 6, Folder 4)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Turkey
- A young female in a long black dress and hat posing in front of garden trellis. Turkish writing on the back. Aleppo, Syria. 13.9 x 8.9 cm, 21 July 1934; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 4)
  Aleppo, Syria; Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Turkish Writing
- A young male in checkered shirt. French and Turkish writing on the back. 12.7 x 8.9 cm, 3 June 1966; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 4)
  Boys; French Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkey; Turkish Writing
- Two young children standing in front of a chair with a vase of roses in front of them. 13.9 x 9.0 cm, 6 May 1978; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 5)
- A male standing in front of a large brick building. Aspendos, Turkey. 11.7 x 8.7 cm, 1965; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 5)
  Antalya, Turkey; Archaeological Sites; Architecture; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Men; Photographic Prints
- An older female in a patterned dress embracing a young boy on a porch. Turkish writing. Sile, Istanbul, Turkey. 11.2 x 8.6 cm, July 1962; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 5)
  Children; Family; Gelatin Silver Prints; Istanbul, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Turkish Writing
- A bald male in a dark coat signing documents with another man in the background. Bakirkoy, Istanbul, Turkey. 14.0 x 8.9 cm, 11 July 1929; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 5)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Istanbul, Turkey; Men; Photographic Prints
- A middle aged female with short dark hair looking off camera in a patterned top. Turkish writing. Studyo Abdi, Yenisehir, Mersin, Turkey. 13.5 x 8.7 cm, 16 February 1973; Studio Abdi, Yenisehir, Mersin, Turkey (Box 6, Folder 5)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Mersin, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkish Writing; Women
- An older male in a three piece suit with white hair with a china cabinet in the background. Altinbakkal, Beyoglu, Istanbul,, Turkey. 14.1 x 9.1 cm, 16 May 1963; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 5)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Istanbul, Turkey; Men; Photographic Prints
- A male holding a snow ball and two females by his side. 14.0 x 8.9 cm., 1963-1964; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 5)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Snow; Turkey
- A male and two females standing behind a water pump. Turkish writing. Uludag, Sarialan, Bursa, Turkey. 13.9 x 9.0 cm, 19 May 1972; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 5)
  Bursa, Turkey; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Nature; Photographic Prints
- A mixed group standing in front of a large statue of Ataturk. Konya, Turkey. 12.9 x 8.4 cm, 1926; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 5)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Konya, Turkey; Military; Mustafa Kemal Ataturk, 1881-1938; Photographic Prints; Statues; Turkey; Uniforms
- An older couple dancing with a lighted pillar in the background. Foto Bayburt, Istanbul, Turkey. 13.4 x 9.1 cm, Undated; Studio Foto Bayburt, Istanbul, Turkey (Box 6, Folder 5)
  Couple; Dancing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Istanbul, Turkey; Party; Photographic Prints
- Two women in white coats holding medical equipment. 11.6 x 8.4 cm, 29 August 1958; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 6)
  Coats; Gelatin Silver Prints; Medicine; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Women
- A group of four men and one woman in a lab coat in a parking lot in front of a large building. 13.9 x 9.0 cm, 1977-78; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 6)
  Coats; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Turkey
- Four females on the front porch of a house, Corlu, Tekirdag, Turkey. 13.9 x 9.1 cm, 20 May 1973; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 6)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Tekirdag, Turkey; Women
- A group of people in summer wear sitting under the shade of a large tree. Sile, Istanbul, Turkey. 11.9 x 9.0 cm, July 1962; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 6)
  Family; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Istanbul, Turkey; Nature; Photographic Prints
- A bride and groom, groom is wearing a turtle neck. Turkish writing on reverse. 13.9 x 8.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 6)
  Couple; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Turkish Writing; Wedding Ceremony
- Three females in winter coats standing in front of three large trees. Armenian writing on reverse. 13.9 x 8.8 cm, 5 July 1933; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 6)
  Armenian Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Nature; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Women
- A group of five men standing in front of the Izmir Kulturpark with Turkish flags on the top. Turkish writing on the back. 13.8 x 8.8 cm, 21 August 1937; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 6)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Izmir, Turkey; Men; Parks; Photographic Prints
- A female in a flower patterned dress sitting in front of a painted backdrop. Foto H. Behcet, Konya, Turkey. 14.0 x 9.0 cm, 26 May 1963; Studio Foto H. Behcet, Konya, Turkey (Box 6, Folder 6)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Konya, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
- Two females in dresses standing in front of a trellis on the wall of a building. Taksim, Istanbul, Turkey. Turkish writing in blue ink on reverse. 13.7 x 8.6 cm, 14 July 1941; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 6)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Istanbul, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Turkish Writing; Women
- A young male laying in bed with a paper crown on his head at his circumcision ceremony. Turkish writing on reverse. 13.0 x 9.2 cm, 18 August 1964; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 6)
  Boys; Ceremony; Circumcisions; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Turkish Writing
- A female in a winter coat sitting on a stone wall in front of a small wooden building. Ottoman writing on the back. 14.0 x 8.8 cm, 19 January 1923; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 7)
  Coats; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Ottoman Writing; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Women
- A family group of six, two young girls are being held by a young woman sitting on a chair. Foto Hilâl, Bakirkoy, Istanbul, Turkey. 13.7 x 8.6 cm, Undated; Studio Foto Hilal, Bakirkoy, Istanbul, Turkey (Box 6, Folder 7)
  Children; Family; Family Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Istanbul, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
- A couple, female in a long silky dress, male in a striped suit. Armenian writing on the back. 13.8 x 9.0 cm, 8 October 1959; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 7)
  Armenian Writing; Couple; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Suits; Turkey
- A female in a long black dress with short wavy hair. Ottoman writing on the back. 13.9 x 9.0 cm, 1931; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 7)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Ottoman Writing; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkey; Women
- A couple, female in a tea length dress, male in a dark double breasted suit. Turkish writing on the back. Sivas. 14.0 x 8.8 cm, 15 September 1946; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 7)
  Couple; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Sivas, Turkey; Studio Photography; Turkish Writing
- A couple, both in dark suits. Turkish writing on the back. 13.5 x 8.5 cm, 4 March 1926; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 7)
- A family group of four, older male seated in a chair. Foto Sen, Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey. Ottoman writing on the back. 13.7 x 8.7 cm, 1941; Studio Foto Sen, Istanbul, Turkey (Box 6, Folder 7)
  Family Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Istanbul, Turkey; Ottoman Writing; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
- A white L-shaped building surrounded by trees and flower beds. Ottoman writing on the back. Yalova, Turkey. 13.6 x 8.5 cm, 1955; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 7)
  Architecture; Buildings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Hotels; Ottoman Writing; Photographic Prints; Yalova, Turkey
- A couple, female is wearing a light dress holding a large flower bouquet. Foto Film, Izmir, Turkey. 13.6 x 8.5 cm, Undated; Studio Foto Film, Izmir, Turkey (Box 6, Folder 7)
  Couple; Gelatin Silver Prints; Izmir, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
- Three males in suits sitting on a park bench with some buildings in the background. Ottoman writing on the back. 14.0 x 8.5 cm, 24 July 1929; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 7)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Ottoman Writing; Parks; Photographic Prints; Turkey
- A family group of four, older male is holding the hand of the younger male in the center. Turkish writing. 13.4 x 8.5 cm, 1 December 1942; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 8)
- A young male in a three piece suit, with a bow at the collar and a mustache. French writing on the back in French. 13.7 x 8.8 cm, 2 February 1926; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Bow Ties; French Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Mustaches; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Suits; Turkey
- Seven males in military uniform in an ever green tree in the countryside. Turkish writing on the back. Bolu, Turkey. 14.0 x 8.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Bolu, Turkey; Countryside; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Military; Photographic Prints; Uniforms
- A young male in a sailor's outfit. Child's writing in Turkish on the back in pencil. 13.4 x 8.3 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Boys; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Maritime Outfits; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkey; Turkish Writing
- A man in a suit kneeling on the floor with his arms raised above his head. Foto Senel, Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey. Sogokart, Armenian Theater. 13.9 x 9.0 cm, 9 April 1961; Studio Foto Senel, Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Men; Performance Plays; Photographic Prints; Theater
- A baby in a white onesy, in a highchair. Photo Porst. Turkish writing. 12.8 x 9.0 cm, 21 August 1968; Studio Photo Porst, Turkey (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Children; Color Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Turkish Writing
- Profile of an older male in a suit. Studio Lale, Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey. Turkish writing. 13.2 x 8.3 cm, Undated; Studio Foto Lale, Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Men; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Suits
- Four males standing in front of a building with a barred window. Turkish writing in black ink. Cankurtaran Train Station, Istanbul, Turkey. 14.0 x 9.0 cm, 12 September 1971; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Istanbul, Turkey; Men; Photographic Prints; Streets; Turkish Writing
- A young male and female standing in front of a bush and a woman seated on a bench. Turkish writing on front and back. 13.9 x 8.7 cm, 1 December 1951; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Parks; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Turkish Writing
- A family group of four, older male is seated, holding the youngest males hand. Foto Istanbul, Karaköy, Istanbul, Turkey. 13.5 x 8.3 cm, Undated; Studio Basin Foto, Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey (Box 6, Folder 8)
- A couple, female in a light satin dress with a large flower arrangement next to them. Foto Park, Izmir, Turkey. Turkish writing in blue ink. 13.9 x 8.8 cm, 3 February 1952; Studio Foto Park, Izmir, Turkey (Box 6, Folder 9)
- A female in a short patterned dress, standing on a small platform with musicians in the background. Foto Raca, Eskisehir, Turkey. 13.7 x 8.5 cm, 20 May 1961; Studio Foto Raca, Eskisehir, Turkey (Box 6, Folder 9)
  Eskisehir, Turkey; Gatherings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Music; Party; Photographic Prints
- A family group with two younger males flanking an older couple. Foto Ihsan, Kasimpasa, Istanbul, Turkey. 13.8 x 8.8 cm, Undated; Studio Foto Ihsan, Istanbul, Turkey (Box 6, Folder 9)
  Family; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Istanbul, Turkey; Photographic Prints
- A female in a striped dress and hat with a flower on it. Foto Raca, Eskisehir, Turkey. 13.8 x 8.6 cm, Undated; Studio Foto Raca, Eskisehir, Turkey (Box 6, Folder 9)
  Eskisehir, Turkey; Gatherings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Hats; Individual Portraits; Party; Photographic Prints; Women
- A family group of four, older female in a skirt suit is seated on a chair. Foto Kamer, Tekirdag, Turkey. 14.0 x 8.8 cm, Undated; Studio Foto Kamer, Tekirdag, Turkey (Box 6, Folder 9)
  Family Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Suits; Tekirdag, Turkey
- Two young males seated on a tree stump. Turkish writing in black in on reverse. Karamursel, Kocaeli. 13.7 x 8.4 cm, 3 March 1936; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 9)
  Boys; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Kocaeli, Turkey; Nature; Photographic Prints; Suits; Turkish Writing
- Three females in skirt suits standing in a grass field with trees in the background. Turkish writing on the back. 13.9 x 8.9 cm, 7 May 1939; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 9)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Nature; Photographic Prints; Suits; Turkey; Turkish Writing; Women
- A couple, female is seated on a chair with a large updo. Foto Milano, Cubuklu, Istanbul, Turkey. 13.8 x 8.7 cm, 4 January 1971; Studio Foto Milano, Istanbul, Turkey (Box 6, Folder 9)
- A mustached man in a three piece suit with tie and a pinky ring on his right hand. Turkish writing. 13.9 x 9.1 cm, 1928; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 9)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Men; Mustaches; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Suits; Turkey; Turkish Writing
- An older female with a head scarf and a young child standing on a chair. Ottoman writing on the back. 14.0 x 8.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 9)
  Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Ottoman Writing; Photographic Prints; Streets; Turkey; Women
- A young female squatting to pick bananas. Turkish writing in blue ink on the back. Alanya, Anatayla, Turkey. 14.0 x 8.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 10)
  Antalya, Turkey; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Women
- A family group standing on a gravel drive way with tall hedges in the background. Writing on reverse. Foto Park. Izmir, Turkey. 13.5 x 8.5 cm, 22 November 1949; Studio Foto Park, Izmir, Turkey (Box 6, Folder 10)
  Family; Gelatin Silver Prints; Izmir, Turkey; Parks; Photographic Prints
- A young male in a three piece suit holding a book, leaning on a pedestal. Turkish writing. 13.5 x 8.4 cm, 6 November 1937; Unknown (Box 6, Folder 10)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Men; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Suits; Turkey; Turkish Writing
- A family group of four, a couple is seated on chairs in front of two females. Foto Turan, Cemberlitas, Istanbul, Turkey. Wedding portrait. 13.7 x 8.5 cm, 11 June 1954; Studio Foto Turan, Istanbul, Turkey (Box 6, Folder 10)
  Couple; Family Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Istanbul, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
- A woman in a flower patterned dress, holding a small baby in a dress and cap on her lap. Foto Yildiz, Uskudar. Camlica, Istanbul, Turkey. Turkish writing on reverse. 13.2 x 8.3 cm, 5 September 1936; Studio Foto Yildiz, Istanbul, Turkey (Box 6, Folder 10)